Please help yourself
Hey, what are you
thinking?
I just…
I guess it's a bit early
to be excited like this
You've worked hard
Let's just celebrate it
for today! Cheers!
Cheers
Were you two
always that close?
Ah
we've been friends
since childhood
But you guys don't
look like just friends…
Did you hurt your hand?
Ah
I got hurt
while cooking
I couldn't bandage it
while shooting…
Wow, do you cook
on your own at home?
Yes
You can come over
some time
We're neighbors, right?
I'd love to
Please cook me
something tasty
Oh, you got something
on your hair
Looks like dust
Hey, where are you going?
Cigarette break
I told you
to quit smoking
Let's smoke together
No, I'm gonna quit
Don't stay too close
to Choi Hyobum
I don't think
that'd happen anyway
Why do you hate him
so much?
Is it because I got
drunk the other day?
Hey, back then, I drank
because I wanted to
On that day…
What?